The problem with wanting to be friends with your children is that this is not enough
Because as parents, you are not less than a friend, you are much higher than that
You are someone who will live your child's life with a little luck
You are a long-term island of stability
In a sea of ​​difficulties
And a child needs that much more than just a friend
Parents answer to be courageous
Because they answer that they let their children make mistakes. You must allow your child to fall while learning to walk
Because they bump into the world a lot and you shouldn't do more to your child
Who is absolutely necessary
This means that it must be accompanied by some rough distance with your love and sympathy
And for that, he must stand away and allow your child
By walking stumbling towards ingenuity. But today's parents are terrified of their children because they are often afraid that they will
They interfered with their children's lives that they would make irreparable mistakes
But you must show the courage of your conviction when you have offspring and understand that if you sin
That you can learn and forgive you for your mistakes. You don't have to be a perfect parent, but you do have to rise above your kids.
Parents are terrified of making mistakes, which means that they are terrified of being parents and this prevents them from being fathers.